Spectacular! is a drama, music, comedy film directed by Robert Iscove.
A high school choir is fading in popularity, as it
continues to lose most of its' members one by one.
A wannabe rock singer is convinced to join the choir, in hopes of
winning the upcoming competition and cash prize.
Nikko Alexander, played by Nolan Gerard Funk.
Courtney, played by Tammin Sursok.
Tammi, played by Victoria Justice.
Royce Da Luc, played by Simon Curtis.
Robin, played by Andrea Lewis.
Eric, played by Harris Allan.
The Spectacular Now is a 2013 American coming-of-age romantic drama film directed by
James Ponsoldt, from a screenplay written by Scott Neustadter and Michael H.
Weber, based on the 2008 novel of the same name by Tim Tharp.
It stars Miles Teller and Shailene Woodley as high-schoolers Sutter and Aimee, whose
unexpected encounter leads to a romance blossoming between the two.
Brie Larson, Mary Elizabeth Winstead, Bob Odenkirk, Jennifer Jason
Leigh, and Kyle Chandler are featured in supporting roles.
The Spectacular Now premiered at the 2013 Sundance Film Festival, and was theatrically released in the United States
on August 2, 2013 where the film garnered critical acclaim, and grossed over $6 million worldwide.
It received two nominations at the 29th Independent Spirit Awards:
Best Female Lead (for Woodley) and Best Screenplay.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.